supportsystem.com 2017-12-20

# Support System

## Privacy Policy

Privacy of our users is critically important to us. SupportSystem respects your privacy and we are committed to protecting your personal information. This notice describes our privacy policy and statement. By utilizing our services, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

**TL; DR** : Your privacy is critically important to us. We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, SupportSystem collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. SupportSystem's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how SupportSystem's visitors use its website. From time to time, SupportSystem may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to SupportSystem’s websites choose to interact with SupportSystem in ways that require SupportSystem to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that SupportSystem gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Those who engage in transactions with SupportSystem – by signing up for an account, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, SupportSystem collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with SupportSystem. SupportSystem does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

SupportSystem may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites for the purose of improving its service offering. SupportSystem may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, SupportSystem does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Personally-Identifying Information

SupportSystem discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on SupportSystem’s behalf or to provide services available at SupportSystem’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using SupportSystem’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. SupportSystem will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, SupportSystem discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when SupportSystem believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of SupportSystem, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an SupportSystem website and have supplied your email address, SupportSystem may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with SupportSystem and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. SupportSystem takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Data Security and Compliance**

The security of our customers’ data is critically important to us. SupportSystem is committed to protecting our customers’ personal and sensitive information above and beyond industry security standards and guidelines. Please see our Compliance Notice for an overview of the steps we take to secure our customers' private information.

**Data Privacy Notice for European Union Website visitors and Customers**

SupportSystem complies with the US EU and US Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks for protecting the privacy of data flowing from the EU and Switzerland to the US, as set forth by the US Department of Commerce. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Enhancesoft’s (SupportSystem's parent company) certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>. Although we are Safe Harbor compliant, do not transmit or transfer data across our EU and US datacenters. Customers can request to be hosted exclusively in our EU based datacenters.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. SupportSystem uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of SupportSystem website, and their website access preferences. SupportSystem visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using SupportSystem’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of SupportSystem’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, SupportSystem may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in SupportSystem’s sole discretion. SupportSystem may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, we encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
